

# **Pavel Grigoryev**

Front-end developer (React/Redux, Shopify)

## Contacts

+375 (29) 393-53-77

Portfolio









## **Skills**

- React, Next.js
- Redux/Redux-Toolkit
- Redux Thunk
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Rest API / Axois
- Formik / React Hook Form
- Jest test / Snapshot test
- Storybook
- Material UI / Ant Design
- HTML5/CSS3/SCSS
- Shopify
- Liquid code
- Wordpress
- Webflow
- o Git
- o Jira
- Figma

### Language

- English intermediate (in progress)
- Russian native
- Belarusian native

# **About Me**

My name is Pavel. I am a civil engineer by profession, but in recent years I have been working as a front-end developer. During this time, I have gained experience working with various projects and teams. My main technology stack includes JavaScript and TypeScript programming languages and frameworks and libraries such as React and Redux. In my free time, I prefer an active lifestyle, I like riding a bike and traveling.

## Experience

#### September 2022 — Present

### Front-end developer

Creating single-page application based on React/Redux/Typescript. Team working. Discussion and creation of application architecture. Adaptive layout. Working with a REST API (CRUD operation). Creating new components and pages with React and Next.js. Managing and updating application state (Redux, RTK, Zustand). Working with forms (login, logout, search, data entry). Working with Git. Projects deploying. Code refactoring, bugs fixing, performance optimization. Tests writing, creating components by Storybook library for testing.

**Stack**: React, Next.js, Redux, Redux-toolkit, React-router-dome, Redux-thunk, Axios, Typescript, Material UI and Design, for Mike, React Hook Form, Storybook, Joke Test, Snapshot Test.

#### May 2023 — June 2023. Online clothing store

#### Front-end developer

Migration an online store from the Shopify platform to the Wordpress platform. Customization a Wordpress theme according design. Development of additional functionality for the site. Teamwork with a UX/UI designer.

Stack: Wordpress, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, PHP.

#### June 2022 — August 2022. Online Business magazine

#### Front-end developer

Creating a news website for a company from scratch on the Wordpress platform. Creating a custom Wordpress theme. Working with forms, setting up sending emails. Implementation of dynamic loading of news on the client side. Teamwork with a UX/UI designer.

**Stack**: Wordpress, Webflow, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, PHP.

## May 2022 — June 2022. Online clothing store

### Front-end developer

Migration an online store from the Shopify 1.0 platform to the Shopify 2.0 platform. Working in a team with a UX/UI designer. After the completion of the project, the download speed of the mobile version of the site increased from 21% to 68%, and the desktop version - from 80% to 94%.

Stack: Shopify, Liquid code, Theme Kit, Shopify CLI, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3.

### November 2021 - April 2022. MTN Haus

## Front-end developer

Creating e-commerce stores on the Shopify platform. Adaptation Shopify extensions in new e-commerce stores. Teamwork using the Kanban methodology.

**Stack**: Shopify, Liquid code, Theme Kit, Shopify CLI, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.

### April 2012 - October 2021. ETM

### Civil engineer

Developing master plans for construction projects

### Education

2022 - 2023. IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer (React/Redux, TypeScript)

2022. ItGid.info: "JavaScript v2.0"

Front-end developer (JavaScript)

2021. FREEMOTE: The Freelance Developer Bootcamp

Front-end developer (Shopify, Liquid code, HTML/CSS/JS)